zaarly.com 2013-05-04

# Privacy Policy | Zaarly

The Zaarly application and the associated Zaarly website available at www.Zaarly.com ("Zaarly") are owned and operated by Zaarly, Inc. ("us" "we" or "our"). The Zaarly application and website provide a platform where you can connect with people in your vicinity who are seeking or providing useful products or services. In addition, Zaarly enables you to keep track of what you like, tell others about what you like, discover new things to try, and find out what your friends enjoy, all in one place (collectively, the “Services”). This Zaarly Privacy Policy (the "Privacy Policy") is intended to inform you of our policies and practices regarding the collection, use and disclosure of any information submitted to us or collected through your use of Zaarly. The information addressed in this Privacy Policy includes "Personal Information," which is information about you that is personally identifiable such as your full name, physical address or e-mail address, as well as "Non-Identifiable Information," which is non-public information that may be associated with or linked to a specific Zaarly account but does not by itself permit the identification of individual persons (e.g., demographic, interest, or site usage information). This Privacy Policy does not pertain to any information that is publicly available on or through Zaarly.

## User Consent

By accessing or otherwise using Zaarly, you agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy and the associated Terms of Service (set forth on http://www.Zaarly.com/tos). You expressly consent to the processing of your Personal Information and Anonymous Information according to this Privacy Policy.

Your Personal Information may be processed by us in the country where it was collected as well as other countries (including the United States) where laws regarding processing of Personal Information may be less stringent than the laws in your country.

## Regarding Children

Children under the age of 13 are not permitted to use Zaarly and we do not intentionally collect or maintain Personal Information from those who are under 13 years old. Protecting the privacy of children is very important to us. Thus, if we obtain actual knowledge that a user is under 13, we will take steps to remove that user's Personal Information from our databases. By using Zaarly, you are representing that you are able to form a binding contract in your jurisdiction.

## Collection and Use of Information

### Information Submitted to Zaarly

In general, we collect both Personal Information and Non-Identifiable Information that you submit to us voluntarily through Zaarly. We collect information that you submit in the process of creating or editing your account and user profile on Zaarly. For example, our registration and login process requires you to provide us with your name, a valid email address and a password of your choice. When using our Application through a mobile device, we will also collect your mobile phone number as part of your registration information. When you personalize your profile and use the features of Zaarly, we will collect any information you voluntarily provide, and we may also request optional information to support your use of Zaarly, including such Non-Identifiable Information as your year of birth, gender and other demographic information. We also collect information in the form of the content that you submit during your use of Zaarly, such as photos, reviews, ratings and other information you choose to submit, including information from other social networks that you choose to link to your Zaarly profile.

If you send an e-mail to us, or fill out our "Feedback" form through Zaarly, we will collect your e-mail address and the full content of your e-mail, including attached files, and other information you provide. When you finalize transactions with other Zaarly users, you will need to submit your credit card or other payment information so that our service providers can process your payment for those products and services. When you participate in contests, sweepstakes, or other activities that we make available on Zaarly, we will collect the information designated along with such activity, which may include your Personal Information to permit us to contact you in connection with that activity. If you choose to sign up to receive information about products or services that may be of interest to you, we will collect your email address and all related information. Additionally, we collect any information that you voluntarily enter, including Personal Information, into any postings, comments, or forums within the Zaarly community.

### Information from Other Sources

We may receive information, including Personal Information, about you from other sources with which you have registered, companies with whom we have partnered (collectively, "Partners") or other third parties. We may associate this information with the other Personal Information we have collected about you. If you connect to Zaarly through another social network, we may collect information about you and your friends from that social network in order to provide you with a more personalized experience. For instance, we may collect your user ID or profile information from that third-party social network that you have permitted to be displayed through Zaarly in order to display you as a friend or in association with your profile and connections. Zaarly will treat this information in the same manner as we treat the information we collect directly from you. However, please remember that the third party providers of such information handle it according to their own privacy policies.

### Information Collected Via Technology

As you use Zaarly, certain technical and usage information may be collected from you, including your Internet protocol address, browser type, and operating system. In connection with your use of the Zaarly Application through a mobile device, we may also gather information from your mobile device including its unique identification number and your geographic location. We also use Cookies and navigational data like Uniform Resource Locators (URL) to gather information regarding the date and time of your visit and the solutions and information for which you searched and viewed, or on which of the advertisements displayed on Zaarly you clicked. This type of information is collected to make Zaarly and its solutions more useful to you and to tailor the Zaarly experience to meet your special interests and needs.

An "Internet protocol address" or "IP Address" is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet. In some cases your IP Address stays the same from browser session to browser session; but if you use a consumer internet access provider, your IP Address probably varies from session to session. We, or our service providers, may track your IP Address when you access Zaarly to assist with ad targeting.

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that a website sends to your computer’s hard drive while you are viewing a website. We may use both session Cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent Cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them) to provide you with a more personal and interactive experience with Zaarly. Persistent Cookies can be removed by following your Internet browser help file directions. In order to use our services offered through Zaarly, your web browser must accept Cookies. If you choose to disable Cookies, some aspects of Zaarly may not work properly, and you will not be able to receive our services.

We may also enable third-party advertising networks, advertisers and ad servers to promote third-party products and/or services by placing advertisements on Zaarly. These advertisers and ad servers may use their own Cookies and/or "Web Beacons" (which are usually small, transparent graphic images) in order to monitor information related to those advertisements and your use of Zaarly. Clicking on such advertisements will direct you to the website of a third-party and the advertiser. This Privacy Policy does not cover the privacy practices of any advertisers or ad servers. For more information about third-party advertising, and to exercise your choices regarding advertising customization by third-party ad networks, visit the Network Advertising Initiative website. (http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

### Aggregate Information

Additionally, we may use your Non-Identifiable Information in connection with compiling Aggregate Information about general site usage in order to perform statistical analysis to help us analyze patterns in the use of Zaarly. Such Aggregate Information will not include your Personal Information.

## Use and Disclosure of Information

### Zaarly’s Use of Information

In general, both the Personal Information and Non-Identifiable Information you submit to us is used to provide you access to Zaarly, to improve Zaarly, to better tailor the features, performance, and support of Zaarly and to offer you additional information, opportunities, promotions and functionality from us, our partners or our advertisers. For example, we may use and display your full name and email address when you send an email notification to a friend through Zaarly or the social network from which you have connected to Zaarly (such as in an invitation, or when sharing your content).

Additionally, we use your email address to contact you on behalf of your friends (such as when someone sends you a personal message or notifications from a social network or other website with whom you have registered to receive such notifications). We may use this e-mail address to contact you, for things such as notifications of limited edition shop sales, changes to Zaarly policies, and other types of service and/or legal notices. You may indicate your preference to stop receiving further promotional communications as further detailed below.

### Zaarly’s Disclosure of Information

Personal Information. Except as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, we do not generally sell, trade, rent, or share the Personal Information that we collect with third parties, unless you ask or authorize us to do so.

Partners and Service Providers: We share your content preferences and other information with the social network from which you have connected to Zaarly, along with those companies and persons with whom you have asked or authorized us to share your information.

We may provide your Personal Information to third-party service providers who work on behalf of or with us to provide some of the services and features of Zaarly and to help us communicate with you. Examples of such services include sending email, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing payments (including credit card payments), and providing customer service. We may share some or all of your Personal Information with our third-party partners, those with whom we have a co-branding or promotional relationship, or other third-parties about whom you are otherwise notified and do not request to opt out of such sharing. We require our third-party service providers to promise not to use such non-public information except as necessary to provide the relevant services to us.

Non-Identifiable Information: This Privacy Policy does not limit our use or disclosure of Non-Identifiable Information in any way, and we reserve the right to use and disclose Non-Identifiable Information to our partners, advertisers and other third parties in our discretion. Specifically, we may use any of the Non-Identifiable Information you provide or that we collect from you or third parties to assist us in recommending content or connections, and we may disclose Non-Identifiable Information to third-parties who assist us in delivering you more relevant advertising and content.

Mergers or Acquisitions/Change of Control: Although we currently do not have a parent company, any subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under a common control, we may in the future, and we may share some or all of your Personal Information with these companies, in which case we will require them to honor this Privacy Policy.

In the event we go through a business transition such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your Personal Information may be among the assets transferred. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur and are permitted by this Privacy Policy, and that any acquirer of ours, or their agents, may continue to process your Personal Information as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

Responding to Legal Process and Related Disclosures: We may disclose your Personal Information if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to (a) comply with laws or to respond to subpoenas, court orders, warrants or other legal demands or to establish or defend Zaarly from legal claims; or (b) to protect and defend our rights or property, you, or third parties from fraud, abuse or violations of the Terms of Service or illegal acts; or (c) to protect the safety or integrity of Zaarly, its users, the public or other parties as it is deemed appropriate, in our sole discretion. You hereby consent to our sharing your Personal Information under the circumstances described herein.

## The Ability Of Others To View You Information

Helping you to protect your information is a vital part of our mission. It is up to you to make sure you are comfortable with the information you choose to provide us and the information you choose to publish. You understand that when you use Zaarly, certain information you post or provide through Zaarly, such as your name, profile, comments, collections and reviews, may be shared with other users and posted on publicly available portions of Zaarly, including without limitation, chat rooms, bulletin and message boards, along with other public forums. Please keep in mind that if you choose to disclose Personal Information when posting comments or other information or content through Zaarly, this information may become publicly available and may be collected and used by others, including people outside the Zaarly community. We will not have any obligations with respect to any information that you post to parts of Zaarly available to others, and recommend that you use caution when giving out personal information to others in public forums online or otherwise. We also share the information you publish with other third parties.

## Third Party Sites and Advertising

Zaarly may contain links to other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such third-party websites. We encourage our users to read the privacy statements of each and every website they visit. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by us through Zaarly and does not apply to these third-party websites. The ability to access information of third-parties from Zaarly, or links to other websites or locations, is for your convenience and does not signify our endorsement of such third-parties, their products, their services, other websites, locations or their content.

## Your Choices Regarding Your Personal Information

We offer you choices regarding the collection, use, and sharing of your Personal Information. When you receive promotional communications from us, you may indicate a preference to stop receiving further promotional communications from us and you will have the opportunity to "opt-out" by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in the promotional e-mail you receive or by contacting us directly (please see contact information below).

Despite your indicated email preferences, we may send you administrative emails regarding Zaarly, including, for example, administrative confirmations, and notices of updates to our Privacy Policy if we choose to provide such notices to you in this manner.

You may change any of your profile information by editing it in the profile settings page. You may request deletion of your Personal Information by contacting us here http://help.zaarly.com/customer/portal/emails/new, but please note that we may be required (by law or otherwise) to keep this information and not delete it (or to keep this information for a certain time, in which case we will comply with your deletion request, only after we have fulfilled such requirements). When we delete Personal Information, it will be deleted from the active database, but may remain in our archives.

## Feedback

If you provide feedback to us, we may use and disclose such feedback for any purpose, provided we do not associate such feedback with your Personal Information. We will collect any information contained in such feedback and will treat the Personal Information in it in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

## Security

We are committed to protecting the security of your Personal Information. We use a variety of industry-standard security technologies and procedures to help protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. Even though we have taken significant steps to protect your Personal Information, no company, including us, can fully eliminate security risks to Personal Information.

## Contact and Revisions

If you have questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy, please contact us here http://help.zaarly.com/customer/portal/emails/new.

This Privacy Policy is subject to occasional revision at our discretion, and if we make any material changes in the way we use your Personal Information, we will post an alert on this page or may otherwise post an alert on Zaarly blog available at http://blog.zaarly.com/corporate. If you object to any such changes, you must cease using Zaarly. Continued use of Zaarly following notice of any such changes shall indicate your acknowledgement of such changes and agreement to be bound by the terms and conditions of such changes.

## Contact us at our headquarters:

Zaarly, Inc.  
14 Mint Plaza, Suite 400  
San Francisco, CA 94103
